I ate seven pints of ice cream this week
and was still able to maintain a caloric
deficit. Here's how I did it. I used my
Ninja Creamy to recreate my favorite ice
cream flavors, but with way lower
calories and much higher protein. Here
are all the flavors that I made this
week. That first one you saw was a Death
by Chocolate. Chocolate base, fudge
brownies, chocolate swirl. Then I did a
Vietnamese iced coffee, which was a
coffee base with some sweet and
condensed milk on top. And then
blueberry pie. This one was absolutely
banging. vanilla base, mixed in some
blueberries, and then topped it with
some villa wafers. Given that I already
had the villa wafers, I did a banana
pudding. This one was highly requested.
Banana pudding base topped with some
whipped cream and some of those vanilla
wafers. Give me this over magnolia any
day of the week. Then I did a strawberry
cheesecake flavor. Reworked this flavor
and it is so much better. It's a
strawberry base with some freeze-dried
strawberries mixed in and then topped
with graham crackers. Then I did a
little Reese's Pieces McFlurry vanilla
base topped with the Quest peanut butter
candies. Basically Reese's Pieces but
with a little bit more protein. And then
I ended off the week with an Oreo
McFlurry. This base vanilla ice cream is
literally 85 calories which means the
Oreos in here are literally more
calories than the actual base itself.
Insane.